Capture:FRM@zxcoon 同步:小福 翻译：感谢我大学的hommie Eddy啊 校对:无伤小子 iTunes：Tearemix 双语合成 Lv&daisy
♪ I'm going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting "howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ Headed on up to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some friends of mine ♪
幻想大陆之战剧情介绍
Previously on Battlestar Galactica.
这是在哪?
What is this place?
这里是幻想大陆
This is Imaginationland!
阿拉!
Allah!
赶快跑啊!
We have to get out of here!
兄弟们等等我啊
Hold on, fellas!
Butters! Butters! Butters! Butters!
那帮恐怖分子刚刚突然袭击了我们的幻想大陆
Terrorists have just attacked our imagination.
如果恐怖分子破坏了那座长墙
If the terrorists blow that barrier,
童话故事中的那些恶灵
all the most evil things ever imagined
就会侵略到我们这来的
are gonna pour out!
阿拉!
Allah! Allah! Allah! - No!
Butters该吃早饭啦!
Butters, time for breakfast.
不要
Ahh, huh?
不要 !
But...
天啊 还好只是个噩梦
Oh, jeez, it was just a dream.
Butters快起床吧
Come on, Butters.
妈妈做了威化饼干
Mom's cooked waffles and 'nanas for you.
噢  吓死我了
Oh, Mom, Dad!
我梦到自己去了个叫幻想大陆的地方
I dreamt I was in Imaginationland
还被恐怖分子抓起来了
and then terrorists attacked it!
这里就是幻想大陆
You are in Imaginationland.
你在做梦!
This is a dream!
啊?
Huh?
喂笨蛋醒醒!
Hey, wake up, stupid!
快醒来啊小屁孩该醒来了!
Come on, wake up, kid!
不要啊我刚刚还躺在自己的房间里呢!
No, wait, I was back home in bed!
你刚刚吓昏过去还尿裤子啦!
No, you passed out and peed your pants!
大家快看恶灵
Look, the evil of Imaginationland
已经过来了!
is coming out!
Ooh! Ahh! Ooh! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
额的娘啊
Oh, hamburgers!
Allah! Allah! Allah! Allah!
Agh! Agh! Agh! Agh!
所有人赶快躲到橡皮糖森林里去啊
Everyone, fall back to the Gumdrop Forest!
跟我来孩子
Come with me, little boy.
我会把你送回家的
I'm going to get you home!
小心啊!异形!
Agh, it's Alien!
逃
Balrghggh!
Agh!
掠夺者!
Predator!
Agh!
Ahh...
Wahghghggh!
Agh!
我们已经把所知的全都告诉你了
Look, we already told you everything we know!
一个人突然变出了个气球
Some guy just showed up in a big balloon
就把我们带到幻想大陆了
and took us into Imaginationland.
我们想知道
What we want to know is how.
我们要找到进入幻想之国的方法
We need to find a way into Imaginationland.
而你们到过那里
You've been there.
你们是怎么去的!
How did you do it?
我们就是乘热气球飞了一段时间
We just... Went on a balloon ride.
肯定是有什么暗门虫洞之类的通道!
There must have been some kind of portal or a doorway.
我们不记得了
Dude, we don't remember.
你们知道发生了什么吗?
Do you realize what's going on here?!
恐怖分子攻击了幻想大陆
Terrorists have attacked our imagination
现在我们的童话世界已经失控了
and now our imaginations are running wild!
所以你们最好能给我想起来点什么!
You better start remembering!
那个暗道是在中国吗?
It was the Chinese, wasn't it?
我们假设中国政府
We've suspected that the Chinese Government
正在建一个通道
was working on a doorway to the imagination.
那就是你们的方法 是吗? - 才不是呢!
Is that where you were?! - No.
少给我装蒜了
That's it, isn't it?
中国的通道在哪
Where do the Chinese keep this portal?
他是怎么运作的快说!
How does it work?
难道他们的比我们的好些吗?!
Is it better than ours?
你们的  ?
Your what?
我们为了打击苏联
Our portal to the imagination built as a secret project
在1962年秘密建造的通道
back to 1962 to fight the Soviets--
嘘 !Tom
Shh, Tom!
那是绝密!
That's super secret.
噢  对不起长官
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
难道美国政府 也有一条通往幻想大陆的通道?
Wait, the U.S. Government has a portal to the imagination?
明白了？
Oh, see?!
干得不赖啊 Tom
Good job, Tom.
你为什么不干脆 把所有计划全部告诉他?!
Why don't you just tell 'em everything about Project "X"?
遵命长官!
Yes, sir.
冷战时期我们建造了一个幻想大陆入口
We built a portal to the imagination
并用他来对付苏联
to use against the Russians during the cold war,
不过他从来
but we never got it--
你他妈说够了没有?
That was sarcasm!
你是在玩弄我吗?! 你个贱人!
I was being sarcastic, you fucking idiot!
十分抱歉 长官
Oh, jeez, I'm really sorry, sir.
既然都已经造好了那个通道
If you already built a doorway to the imagination,
为什么还来找我们呢?
then why do you need us?
看来应该要给他们看看了
All right, we might as well show it to them.
Tom 操你妈的
Goddamn it, Tom.
每天晚上我会做同一个梦
Every night the dream is the same.
我正走在拜访Kyle的路上
I'm on my way to visit my friend Kyle,
我们曾经打赌
because we had a bet
如果我找到了妖精
that if I could prove leprechauns were real,
他就得舔我的老二
he would suck my balls.
结果我找到了
And it turns out I was right.
到你履行诺言的时候了 Kyle
Time to pay up, Kyle.
但
but then...
不!
No!
他就这样离我而去我
It's been taken from me.
就这样我的蛋蛋越来越干燥 失去了水分
I have dry balls.
最后他们就像烟尘一样 在空气中飘散
Balls so dry they explode like dust.
Aahhh...
不要!不要!
Ahh, ahh!
你还好吧孩子?
You okay, kid?
不好
No.
我的蛋蛋正在迅速失水 时间就快不够了
I've got dry balls, and I'm running out of time.
自从冷战开始
Ever since the cold war,
美国政府就秘密着手研究
the U.S. Government has been working on a secret project
一个通往梦幻国度的通道
to build a doorway into the imagination.
这个秘密计划的代号是: 去往梦幻国度的通道
It is called "Project Imagination Doorway."
恩这个代号好像没什么创意
That's not very imaginative.
根据在这个研究实验中所搜集到的信息
According to all the tests and the data,
通道应该可以正常运转
the doorway should work.
但他从来没有工作过
But it never has.
不过我们已经很接近了长官
But we're close, sir.
十分接近
We're real close.
这话他已经说了40年
They've been saying that for over 40 years.
你们就是那几个
You're the ones, right?
从梦幻国度回来的孩子吧?
The kids that have been inside the imagination?
应该没错吧
I guess.
你们经过了什么特殊的步骤才进去的吧
What was the sequence that got you inside?
我们发现进入梦幻国度需要一段代码
We know there's some kind of resonance code,
不过至今也没有找到
but we can't figure it out.
我们就看到一个家伙
Look, we're sorry, you guys,
然后和他一起上了个热气球
but the balloon just went up in the air,
他开着气球还唱了首歌
and the dude sang a song
我们就到了
and we were suddenly there.
一首什么样的歌?
What song?!
想像之歌
The imagination song.
可能就是那首歌了
That could be it!
那个通道从来没有工作可能
The fractal converter has never worked
可能就是没有那段代码!
because it was waiting for a multi-tonal code!
快!那首歌是怎么唱的?
Quick, boys, how does the imagination song go?
♪ Imagin-a-tion ♪
长官通道有反应了 有电流信号通过!
Sir, I'm getting some electro feedback from the gate.
它 它很微弱
It's weak but it...
像是对某种代码的反应
It's nano-responding to something.
后面还有吗?
Was there more to the imagination song?
剩下的是怎么唱的?
How does the rest of it go?
♪ Imag-in-a-tion ♪
♪ Imagina-- ♪
不对我记得这里是升调
No, no, dude, it went up there.
♪ Imagina-- ♪
我们不记得了
Dude, we don't remember.
这歌实在是太傻逼了
It was really long and stupid.
我可不会和你们玩游戏
I'm just about through playing with you boys!
就要没时间了!
We're running out of time.
你们最好给我唱出来! 包括声调
You have to remember that song in its entirety!
市长
Mayor!
市长我们现在该怎么办?
Mayor, what are we supposed to do?
不要死啊
Please, sir!
我还要回到自己的世界啊!
I have to get home to my world!
恩你只要
Oh, well, all you have to do
后脚跟相击3次就可以了
is tap your heels together three times.
真的吗?
Really?
假的!你个傻逼这就是个小笑话!
No, you fucking dipshit, that was a joke!
Ahghg!
Ahghghghg!
市长我们该怎么办啊?
Mayor, what are we supposed to do?
Snarf, snarf.
阳光城堡
Get to Castle Sunshine.
那是你们唯一希望
It's your only hope!
阳光城堡?
Castle Sunshine?
穿过橡皮糖森林就到了
Through the Gumdrop Forest.
幸存的人都会躲到那里
Others will be hiding there.
走快走
Go, run!
小心那些恶灵!
Look out for the evil characters!
他们都聚集在咩咩山上了
They're assembling on the Yum Yum Mountain.
Blah-bleh.
我们自由了
We are free!
梦幻国度是我们的了!
Now all of Imaginationland is ours.
还没有呢兽人傻逼
Not all, foolish Orc.
我们还
There are still parts of Imaginationland
没有完全掌控这里呢!
we don't control.
明天就开始在这
Tomorrow, we shall build our own castle
建造我们自己的城堡吧
right on this spot.
谁说你当头了?
Who put you in charge, Kruger?
我才是这最邪恶的人!
I am the most evil character here.
瞎扯蛋吧
Nonsense!
你早过时了!
Your evil is stale.
我才是这最邪恶的角色!
I am the most evil imaginary character!
哼
Hiss!
嗨 都过来吧
Now, come on, y'all.
我们别吵了
We shouldn't be fighting.
我们和你们是一边的
We're supposed to all be on the same side.
恩 对 疯狂松鼠
Yeah, you're right, Squirrely Squirrel.
对耶!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
他们是哪个故事里面的角色?
What evil imaginary characters are they?
他们来自某个4年级小学生的
They were dreamt up by some fourth grade kid
圣诞故事
as part of his Christmas story.
大家听我说
Now, come on, y'all.
别在争吵上浪费时间了
We can't waste time arguing.
可能这附近还有幸存者
There could still be survivors out there.
我们要把他们找出来干掉
We need to hunt them down and kill them.
再吸他们的血!
And eat their flesh.
恩不过先要鸡奸他们!
But first we should rape them.
要不我们先杀了他们再奸尸
How about we kill them, and then rape their bodies
这样他们的血正好可以当润滑油!
so we can use their blood as lubricant?
恩那可是个好主意恐惧熊
Say, that's a great idea, Beary Bear!
一场血腥的狂欢
A blood orgy!
我可不希望碰到那个
Man, I do not want to meet the kid
创造出这些家伙的小孩
that dreamt those things up.
听着你们怎么也要给老子个说法!
Look, I want some Goddamned answers.
你们把我朋友绑架到了华盛顿
You brought my friend here to Washington!
现在他在哪里? 到底怎么了?
Where is he? What is going on?
很抱歉先生我无可奉告
I'm sorry, sir.
那是机密
That information is classified.
到底发生什么了?
Something is going on,
听着我有权知道我的朋友在哪里!
and I have a right to know where my friend is!
这有个人使劲提问 不停的问
There's somebody asking a lot of questions
到底发生了什么
about what's going on.
让我来处理吧
Let me handle this.
对不起这没什么
I'm sorry, but there is no such thing as
"幻想大陆通道"计划!
"Project Imagination Doorway."
"幻想大陆通道"
"Imagination Doorway."
一项始于60年代的政府秘密计划等等
It was started in the '60s as a secret government project.
对!
Right.
♪ Imagin-a-tion ♪
♪ Imagin-- ♪
在这有一个小小的变音
Wait, wait, maybe that was where he went really flat,
要降半个调
like that half step key change.
IMAGINATION
♪ Imagin-ation ♪
对 下一句是
Right, then it was...
♪ Imagination ♪
♪ Imagin-a-tion ♪
通了!
It's open, it's open!
他开始工作了!我接到了另一边的信号了!
Getting readings from the other side.
好了
That's it.
幻想大陆通道打开了长官
We've made an opening to our imagination, sir!
好了
Woo-hoo! Yeah! All right! Woo-hoo!
够了别高兴的太早
All right, that's enough!
还有更多的工作等着我们呢!
We've still got a lot of work to do, people.
现在是时候
It's time to go in
去控制梦幻国度了!
and get our imaginations under control.
还要走多远才能到阳光城堡啊?
How much further to Castle Sunshine?
Snarf!
我也不知道啊 Snarf Snarf
I'm not sure-- snarf, snarf!
我从来没去过那里
I've never been.
啊
怎么了?
What was that?
在那边
Over here.
天啊 那是草莓娃娃
Oh, Christ, it's Strawberry Shortcake!
Ha-ha! Ha-ha! Ah-ha-ha! Ah-ha-ha!
求求你们了放了我吧
Please, let me go!
Ogh!
Agh!
啊  天啊 Snarf
Oh, my God! Snarf!
杀了她!
Now kill her!
嘿嘿 大家都等等
Whoa, whoa, hang on, y'all.
不能让她死这么舒服
You can't just kill her.
这样一点都不邪恶啊!
That's not evil enough.
你准备怎么办?
What do you mean?
我们已经挖了她的眼球了
We cut out her eyeball.
恩 口味已经够重啦
Yeah, that's super hard-core.
来吧
Now, come on, y'all.
让我们做得更好
We can do better than that.
恩我觉得
Hey, I know!
我们可以往她的眼窝撒尿
Let's all pee in her empty eye socket!
我觉得可以先让她吃了自己的眼珠
Let's make her eat her own eyeball
然后再灌尿到眼窝里去
and then pee in her empty eye socket.
其实我们可以找个艾滋病人
How about we get someone with A IDS
往她眼窝里撒尿
to pee in her eye socket
这样她就会死得又慢又痛苦的
so she dies all slow like?
好耶!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
这可没人有艾滋 !
Nobody here has A IDS!
哎
Aww! Aww! Aww! Aww!
不过我们必须要找有艾滋的人啊
But we've got to have A IDS
在尿她眼窝之前
before we pee in her eye socket.
别担心
Now, don't be down y'all.
我敢肯定在这个森林里总能找到艾滋病人的
I'll bet we can find some A IDS out in the forest!
好耶!
Yay! Yay! A IDS! - Yay!
快跑
Go, run, run, run!
大兵们给我听着 我不知道你们将在通道的
All right, men, we don't know what you'll experience
另一边遇到什么
on the other side of this doorway,
不过可以肯定 你们在那边的遭遇将会很奇怪
but it will most likely be really weird.
如果你们真的进入了幻想大陆 你们要
If you reach our imagination, you are to take
使用一切必要手段恢复幻想大陆的秩序
every step necessary to get it under control.
都准备好了吗?
Are you ready?!
是的 长官
Yes, sir! Yes, sir! Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
Are you ready, Kurt Russell?
你准备好了吗 KURT RUSSELL?(海神号男主角)
我就是不知道自己是来这干嘛的
I... I don't understand why I'm here.
我只是个演员啊
I'm just an actor.
对你曾经在电影里
Yes, but you were in that one movie
遇见过这样的情景 (他曾主演"星际之门")
that was kinda like this.
所以你比别人更有经验
That gives you more experience than anybody.
好了出发吧!
All right, here we go!
大兵们前进!
Men, forward...
长官有个安全警报
Sir, we have a security breach!
什么?
What?!
一个非法入侵者
There's an unauthorized entry alert.
在二区
It's coming from sector two.
二区  ?
Sector two?
Baghhh!
Cartman?
哈啰 Kyle
Hello, Kyle.
你认为自己可以逃脱惩罚吗?
Thought you could get out of your responsibilities, huh?
你他妈到底是谁?
Who the hell are you?!
他和我打赌
That kid you have made a bet with
如果我见到的真是妖精
that if I could prove I saw a leprechaun,
他就要舔我老二!
he would suck my balls.
把他给我扔出去!
Get him out of here!
嘿 等等
No, hold on a second!
老子可是有判决书的!
I have a contract validated by
国家法律都证明了!
the United States court system!
拿来给我看看
Let me see that.
你怎么会答应舔人家老二呢?
Why would you agree to suck someone's balls?
我根本就不相信天下真会有
I didn't think there was gonna be
那狗屁妖精!
a Goddamned leprechaun!
好吧 你们先去会议室里解决了吧
All right, you two can go use the conference room.
快点 我们还有很多事情呢!
Go on, we have work to do here.
什么
What?!
嘿 我想留在这看事情的进展呢!
Well, wait, I wanna see what happens here!
你可是签了字的
You signed an agreement, kid.
我们可没时间在这磨蹭
We don't have time for this.
按照协议去做吧
Go on and do it.
Stan?
兄弟那可是签上你大名的
Dude, you did make a deal.
那么   会议室该往那边走捏?
The conference room is which way?
哎 哎 哎 是时候了 Kyle
Well, well, well, here we are, Kyle.
你想逃避我们的约定
You tried to bail on our agreement
不过还好我找到你了
but I found you.
我才没逃避!
I didn't bail.
我是被政府给搞来这的
I got picked up by the government.
不过我还是找到你了
Well, we're here now.
这才是最重要的
That's all that matters.
来点坚果吗?
Care for some nuts?
哦 对了 我想你的嘴里很快就会
Oh, that's right, I guess you'll be chock-full of nuts
塞满别的东西的
in just a few minutes.
Cartman 你知道发生了什么吗?
Cartman, do you even know what's going on?
我们到了幻想大陆 还被恐怖分子给袭击了
We went to Imaginationland, terrorists attacked it,
现在政府准备
and now the government is about to--
不好意思啊Kyle
oh, jeez, I'm sorry, Kyle.
这个故事烦透了
It's just I'm so completely bored by this story.
你知道吗?我注意到在这个故事里
See, I'm really only interested in the part
妖精是存在的
where the leprechaun was real
所以你就必须舔我老二!
and so you have to suck my balls.
好 其实你什么都不了解
Okay, fine-- you know what?
先赶紧把这事情做个了结吧
Let's just get it over with.
嘿   嘿   嘿 这可没那么简单 Kyle
Oh, no, no, no, not so fast, Kyle.
这一刻我已经等了很久了
I've waited a long time for this,
我要将他详细的记录下来
and I intend to savor each and every second.
听着我可是认真的
No, I'm serious.
我要看看大厅里将会发生什么
I wanna see what's happening downstairs,
我们赶紧做个了结吧!
so let's just do it.
没这么快呢 Kyle
Not just yet, Kyle.
我还要点时间做下准备
There's still a few things I need to do.
还有件事情要告诉你
By the way, I should tell you
我为了找你都没洗澡的
that I haven't had a chance to shower
在这一路上
while making my way up here.
我老二应该会有点酸
My balls are... Extra vinegary.
你就快点吧 !
Just get to it already!
5秒后进入通道
Entering the portal in five seconds!
Kurt Russel最后再做个无线电检查
Kurt Russell, can I get a com check?
好一   二
Check one, two.
好运大兵们
Good luck, men!
一路平安!
And Godspeed!
情况怎么样了?
What do we have?
Kurt Russel能听到我说话吗?
Kurt Russell, can you hear me?
我们已经到了!
We're here!
我们到了
We're somewhere.
他们已经到幻想大陆了长官
They are inside the imagination, sir.
在那看到什么了?
What do you see in there?
这有很多大蘑菇五颜六色的草
There's lots of big mushrooms and colorful grass,
远处还有一些城堡
some castles in the distance.
等等有东西正往这边过来
Wait... Something's coming for us!
它们从要从草丛里出来了!
It's coming out of the bushes!
那是
It-- it's a...
Oh.
哦 就是只可爱的小松鼠
Oh, it's just a cute little squirrel.
嘿 它说话了
Hey, it talks!
会说话的小松鼠
Ha-ha, the little squirrel talks.
呵 一只想像出来会说话的小松鼠
Aw, an imaginary talking squirrel.
噢
Aww! Aww! Aww! Aww!
问问那小松鼠关于
Ask the squirrel what it knows about
恐怖袭击的消息
the terrorist attack.
等等
Wait a minute.
小松鼠还有很多朋友
The squirrel has friends.
哦 是一群可爱的森林小动物
Oh why it's a whole bunch of woodland critters.
等等 森林小动物
Wait, woodland critters.
有会说话的熊海狸 嘿
There's a talking bear and a beaver.
他们看起来好像是圣诞节小宠物
They seem to be Christmas critters.
噢 哈啰 !
Oh, hello!
他们好热情啊
Yes, hi!
要他们赶快离开!什么?
Get them out of there! - What?
要他们赶快跑!
Tell them to get away now!
到底他妈怎么了?
What's the matter?
噢 可爱的小熊的
Oh, the cute little bear,
眼睛开始变红了
his eyes are starting to glow red now.
喔 你好啊小动物们
Hello there, little animals.
你们知道这里发生了
Do happen to know how-- ahghgh!
Ahghghghghghh!
Kurt Russel发生了什么?
Kurt Russell, what's going on!?
他们在鸡奸我  !他们在鸡奸我  !
They're raping me! They're raping me!
赶快跑 Kurt Russel
Get out of there, Kurt Russell!
我们全都被鸡奸啦  !
They're raping all of us!
啊   啊   疼死啦
Agh, oh, it hurts!
他们在鸡奸我们 疼死啦 太疼啦
They're raping us and it hurts!
Ahh!
♪ Da da-da da da-da-da ♪
我觉得用
I was thinking about using
快速曝光和浅景会好些
a high-speed shutter with a low depth of field.
你觉得怎么样  ?
What do you think?
你他妈的就别浪费时间了好不?!
Goddamn it, Cartman, will you stop wasting time.
我就想快点做个了结!
I want to get this over with!
恩没错Klye
No, you're right, Kyle.
高曝光更加可以
A higher depth of field will make sure
突出重点
everything stays in focus.
差不多了
There we go.
开始吧Kyle当你在舔我老二的时候
Now, Kyle, when you're sucking my balls,
你是会想到
are you gonna think about
我关于妖精的独到见解
how right I was about the leprechaun,
或者只是专心于
or are you just gonna try and focus on
细细吸吮我咸糙的老二呢?
how rough and salty my balls feel in your mouth?
你他妈就快点开始吧!
Let's just do it!
别急嘛 Kyle
In time, Kyle.
你一直在焦急的渴望着老二对吗?
You certainly are eager for balls, aren't you?
看来你是有那么点点老二饥渴症啊
Are you ball famished? Ball starving?
其实我觉得在这一刻
You see, Kyle, I wonder if at this moment
你应该会
you're actually--
所有人到大厅集合 就是现在
Everyone to the main hall now!
快!
Go!
别别 我们还没好呢
Uh, no, no, we're not done in here yet.
所有人到大厅集合赶快!
Everyone to the main hall now!
No!
啊   操他娘的!操!
Goddamn it, no!
嘿 孩子 Snarf Snarf
Oh, boy-- snarf, snarf.
我腿都走酸了 Snarf
My feet are really getting tired-- snarf.
哦Snarf 你就不能
Uh, Snarf, could you maybe like
安静一会吗?
shut up for five minutes?
嘿 等等 已经到了 我们成功了!
Wait, there it is, we made it!
阳光城堡
Castle Sunshine!
-耶!太好啦! -耶!太好啦! -耶!太好啦!
Yeah! All right! - Snarf!
赶快快躲进去!
Hurry, get inside!
恶灵已经在这附近了
The evil imaginary characters are approaching!
关上城门
Lock down the gates!
准备好大炮!
Prepare to fire the cannons!
等等 等等
Wait, wait!
你们是什么哪个童话里的人物?
What imaginary character are you?
我是从棒棒糖森林里来的棒棒糖国王
The Lollipop King from the Lollipop Forest.
我是Snarf
And I'm Snarf.
Snarf, snarf, snarf, snarf.
你又是什么童话人物呢?
And what imaginary character are you?
呃 我不是什么童话人物
Oh, uh, I'm not imaginary.
我是Butters
I'm Butters.
"Butters"是什么?
What's a Butters?
市长把他和其他几个孩子一起
The mayor brought him and some other kids
带来这的
into Imaginationland
在恐怖分子袭击之前
just before the terrorists attack.
你是从真实世界过来的?
So you came from the real world
和恐怖分子在同一时间
at precisely the same time as the terrorists?
难道就只是个巧合?
That seems like quite a coincidence.
我就是在和朋友们一起玩
I-- well, I was just playing with my friends,
然后抓住了一个妖精 然后我们
and then we caught a leprechaun, and then--
原来是你抓了矮妖精!
you caught the leprechaun?
把他抓起来!
Take him!
波尔修斯 (他是宙斯的儿子英仙座) 他不是坏人啊 Snarf Snarf
Perseus, he's not against us-- snarf, snarf.
快说到底怎么了?
Talk to me-- what's going on?
有东西  在从通道里   往这边来
Something is coming through the gate from the other side.
Rahghg!
这是什么啊?!
What is it?!
看起来像人熊
It's like a half man half bear!
还有猪!
And half pig!
Arahgh!
Agh!
噢 不对   等等
No, no, wait!
它像熊人猪  !
It's like a half bear, half man-pig!
Argah!
小心!
Look out!
不对 我觉得它更像人猪熊!
No, I think it's more like a half man and half pig-bear.
反转通道把它送回去!
Reverse the doorway, send it back through!
Aah!
Kyle!
嘿 我没有帮助恐怖分子
Please, I didn't help the terrorists
来这的啊
get into Imaginationland.
真的!
Honest!
这可是九人议会说的算
That is for the Council of Nine to decide.
别担心孩子
Don't worry, kid.
九人议会是
The Council of Nine consists of some of
最受尊敬的角色
the most highly regarded imaginary characters
在幻想大陆中
in all Imaginationland.
议员兄弟们
Fellow council,
现在黑暗时代已经降临
these are indeed dark times.
恶灵正在城门外集结
The evil forces amass at our gates as we speak.
宙斯觉得我们应该撤离
Zeus believes we should evacuate.
没错 他们强于我们太多
Yes, their power outmatches ours.
如果他们肯放我们走的话 我们应该撤离
If they are giving us a chance to leave we must take it.
你觉得呢 墨菲斯?
And what say you, Morpheus?
不过谁知道他们真肯放过我们呢?
How are we to know that they will let us go?
这可能是个圈套
Their offer could be a trap.
也许我们应该撤到alderon神庙
Perhaps we must flee to the Temple of Alderan.
他们总追不到那里去吧?
Surely they wouldn't chase us there.
不行 我们不能逃走
No, we can't.
大家好好想想啊这是我们的家
Come on, you guys, this is our home.
战斗阻止恶灵的侵略 我们要保卫家园啊!
We have to fight to keep it the way it is meant to be.
我和耶稣的看法一样
I'm with Jesus.
那些恶灵肯定不会轻易放过我们的
The evil characters aren't going to just let us go.
!@#$%^&*这样问题就*&^%$#@!$
Gets 'skim ta truffleup?
也许你是对的大力水手 不过难道我们还有选择吗?
That may be, Popeye, but we don't have a choice.
Ahem...
九人议会请原谅我的鲁莽
Forgive my intrusion, Council of Nine.
这个孩子是从真实世界渗透过来的
But this boy has infiltrated from the real world.
带他过来
Bring him here!
电击!
Clear!
对不起 我已经尽力了
I'm sorry, he's gone.
不 Kyle不能死
No, Kyle can't die.
抱歉孩子
I'm sorry, young man.
Kyle
恩 起码他现在不用
Well, at least now he doesn't have to
吸某人的老二了
suck anyone's balls.
不!
No!
他从不软弱
No, he has a strong heart!
他渴望生存!
He wants to live!
加油 Kyle快啊 加油 我的兄弟!
Come on, Kyle, come on, buddy!
他已经死了 孩子
He's gone, little boy.
电击快!
Zap him again!
电击快!充电中
Do it! Charging.
快电!
Do it!
加油兄弟 加油!
Come on, buddy, Come on, buddy! - Clear!
滚开我来
Get out of here!
你他妈的 Kyle
Goddamn it, Kyle,
你永远不会离开我们的!
you've never walked away from anything in your life!
振作 振作 振作
Now fight, fight!
振作起来啊!
Fight right now!
振作振作振作  !
Fight, fight, fight!
给他输氧
Get him some air!
呼吸放松呼吸
Easy, breathe easy.
我觉得这孩子的到来
I believe this child was brought into Imaginationland
一定是有原因的
for a reason.
大概市长知道些什么 我们还不了解的信息
Perhaps the mayor knew something we don't.
那你是什么意思 阿斯兰?
What are you saying, Aslan?
如果我们要夺回这个国家 就要
That if we are to take back control we might--
没错 如果我们想要
Yes, if we are to take back control
从恶灵手中夺回国家
from the evil forces,
这个孩子也许就是救世主
this little boy might be the key.
哦   我是救世主 ?
Aww, I'm the key?
我可以不当什么救世主吗墨菲斯?
Could I not be the key, Morpheus?
我不想当什么救世主
I don't wanna be the key.
如果你还想看到自己的家孩子
If you ever wanna see your home again, little boy,
你就必须接受这项挑战
you'll have to rise to this challenge.
我本应该是在学校上课
But I'm supposed to be at school right now.
而不是对着大力水手
Instead I've got Snarf, I've got Popeye
和天行者 (小声)真烦
and Luke Skywalker all pissed off...
现在是所有人的黑暗时期
It is a dark time for all of us, young boy.
不过如果你相信自己
But know that if you believe in yourself,
情况就会好起来的
everything will turn out all right.
长官你确定要这样做了吗?
Sir, are you sure about this?
我们没有选择
We have no choice.
恐怖分子袭击了我们最脆弱的地方
Terrorists have attacked us where we are most vulnerable.
没有别的方法解决了
There's no other option.
只有把那片土地给"和谐"了
We have to nuke our imagination.
醒醒 Kyle
Wake up, Kyle.
welcome to www.1000fr.com